Guide to the Juan Felipe Herrera Papers, ca. 1970-1998 M1043
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 6: Photographs and Slides
  - Subseries 1: United States
    - 2 fotos of Mujeres Muralistas (by Yolanda M. Lopez, 1977, San Diego, Ca. Chicano Park); Centro Cultural de La Raza, Balboa Park, San Diego, Ca. 1974 (by Memo Cavada). (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Two B & W fotos by Yolanda M. Lopez. 1) Las Mujeres Muralista / young Chicana women from San Diego, late 70's 2) Couple from Mission District, SF early 80's. with envelope. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Lopez, Yolanda.Camera ready foto of "Tres Mujeres" for Citybender Broadside publication. San Diego, Ca. 1978. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Foto of Francisco X. Alarcon (center) & Renato Rosaldo (profile Ori"right) in Cuba. 1979. JFH foto­credit. [Moved to photo box 16]. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Francisco X. Alarcon color Xerox of photo by JFH, Havana, Cuba, 1979. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - 40 color slides of the Underground Chicano Winter Onda event at Stanford University. Organized by JFH & Francisco X. Alarcon. with poets: Alurista, Gloria Ve!asquez-Trevino, Marialupe Duarte, Ricardo Mendoza, Javier Pacheco and Teatro Cábula (Rogelio "Smiley" Rojas & Olivia Chumacero) and mural art backdrop by Mario Torero" Acevedo. 1979. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - 3 sets: a) Teatro de La Calle, Sacramento, Ca. 1979-81 (Richard Montoya at center); b) Teatro Latino, SF, Ca. 1979-81; c) Maria Gaitan (San Francisco Mime Troup, SF, Ca.) and Maria Gaitan (typist) with teatro Chicano at a Regional Tenaz festival in San Diego, Ca./San Diego City College. 1973-4. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Paste-up art, negatives, photos (Featro Latino, SF, Alfredo Arreguin, Seattle, Camera ready half-tones (Patricia Rodriguez, Rupert Garcia art. 1980-3; fotos and negatives by Maria Pinero (SF Photographer), used for Metamorphosis Magazine (Univ. Wa., Seattle). (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Five fotos: 1) Wilfredo Q. Castano, poet at the 1st Annual Monopoem festival, SF Ca. Project Artaud 1981 Organized by JFH and Francisco Alarcon. 2) Los Mascarones, Mexico City Political theatre at the 11th Tenaz teatro Festival, SF, ca Foto, JFH. 3) Orlando Ramirez (left) and Pedro Ramirez (right) poets at the 1st Annual Monopoem festival, SF. Ca.4) Teatro rehearsal of YO PUEDO SUMMER PROGRAM students at UC Santa Cruz. 1985. Directed by Olivia Chumacero. 5). Foto of Poetasumanos project: Ricardo Mendoza, San Diego Poet, reading on 24th Street, Mission District, SF 24th Street Fair 1980 Foto" Gustavo Vasquez. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Monopoem Festival, SF, Ca. Project Artaud bldg. a) Tede Matthews, b) Conyus, c) Emy Lopez, d) John Marron; 1981[?]. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - 5 photos by Phillipe Bourgeois, Stanford anthropology student at the time / Salvadorean refugees in camps in Honduras after suffering massacre in La Cabanas, El Salvador. 1981. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Foto of JFH, Margarita Luna Robles, reading at the Federal Bldg. cinco de mayo, 1982. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - 5 b/w photos by Maria Pinedo (San Francisco, Ca.). Various subjects. 1982. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - 42 color duplicates of Graphics/ Poetry workshop by JFH (Calif Arts Council funded) at the Galeria de la Raza, SF, Ca. 1983. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Nine color slides of student poetry-poster-books. from JFH Poetry-Grafik workshop at La Galeria de La Raza, SF Ca 1983-84 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - B & W foto of JFH, 1985, taken by Margarita Luna Robles, 1985, San Jose Avenue, San Francisco, Ca. and large half-tone of Yolanda M. Lopez's foto used for Exiles of Desire Cover (1983). (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Two fotos of "Young Boxer" by Salvador Garcia, artist. SF.ca. mid-80's. for Gato's Journal. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Almasol Herrera (daughter). 1985. San Francisco, Ca. Old fotos of uncles (Geno, Chente and Roberto Quintana/ Back row, left to right): Fort Bliss, El Paso, Texas, 1920-22. (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - 36 color slides of Flor y Canto Poetry festival at Casa Zapata, Stanford organized by Jose Antonio Burciaga. 1986. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Various: a) JFH in San Francisco, Ca. Galeria de La Raza, by Yolanda M. Lopez. 1984. ) b) "Funky Household Blues & Comedy Revue" cast. San Francisco, Ca. MIssion District. 1986. foto by Emmanuel Montoya. (Left to right: Margarita Luna Robles, Felix Alvarez, Richard Talavera, JFH, Dominique di Prima, c) 6 prints of JFH/ Margarita Luna Robles & Carlos Gonzalez (congero) at the Federal Bldg. SF, Ca. 14th floor. 5/5 / 82; d) Teatro Chicano/ CSU-Fresno JFH class at Fresno High. 1992. e) Color Xerox of Mamkrucirco production of "Orientationation Cafe" (JFH) at CSU-Humboldt, Arcata. 1994; f) 5th Tenaz Teatro Chicano Festival/ 1st Latin American Teatro Festival. Teotihucan (opener). JFH with drum & Mario Aguilar (violin) and Alurista (concha). 6/1974. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - 9 photos by Joaquin Ryan (son in New York) / class project. 1988-89. (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Foto of Phoebe Scherrer (Iowa poet) and husband. 1990. (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Two b/ w fotos of Teatro Zapata (CSU-Fresno, JFH class) performing a play at Fresno High School, Fresno. Ca. 1992. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Photos proofs of my Chicano Writers Workshop. CSUF. 1994. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Teatro Zapata: CSU-Fresno. JFH class. Proofs of Teatro members. Spring 1998. Luz Hernandez, Rocio Magana, Felix Alvarez, Norma Gonzalez, Albert Gonzalez, Aida Gonzalez. And Group shots. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Three different xeroxes of Mexican movie actress, Lupe Velez. Image for poetry experiments. One foto of SF waterfront bathroom; n.d. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous photos: Poetry reading at Galeria de la Raza, n.d.; outdoor class exercise at CSU-Fresno, n.d.; JFH, Margarita Luna Robles, and two others, unidentified, n.d.; unidentified man, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 2 photos by Wilfredo Q. Castaflo (SF poet, photographer), late 1970s (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2: Trip to Mexico 1970
    - 2 prints. Totonaca Indians. Tuxpam, Ver. Mexico. Ceremonia del palo Volador. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - 14 b/ w prints (1 half-tone) of El Colorin Village, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mex. 1970. Huichol Indians. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Mounted b/ w prints: 2 of San Juan Chamula. Chiapas, Mex. 1970. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - 1 mounted print: Huichol girl. El Colorin, Nayarit, Mexico. 1970. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - 24 b / w prints of Tzotzil Indians in San Cristobal de las Casas, Chiapas and Municipios. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Selva Lacandona, Chiapas: a) 1993 & b) 1970 (Nahá & Lacanjá Chan Sayab). 17 prints. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - 4 Huichol Indian prints: EL Colorin, Nayarit, Mex. 1970. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - 11 mounted prints: Tzotzil Indians, San Cristobal de Las Casas, Municipios. Chiapas, Mex. 1970. (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - 1 print of Cora Indian. Instituto Nacional Indigenista, Tepic, Nayarit. Mexico, 1970. (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - 5 prints of Nahá, Selva. 5 of San Cristobal de Las Casas. Chiapas, Mex. 1970. (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - 24 b/ w finished prints of El Colorin, Huichol Indian Village, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mex. 1970. Ramon Medina Silva's village. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - 18 prints used in Mayan Drifter (Temple University Press, 1997). Father, Felipe Emelio Herrera and others of Chiapas, particulary the Selva Lacandona. (1993). (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - 330 original and duplicate color slides of Mexico 1970 project (Huichol, Totonaca, Lacandon Maya, Tzotzil) and other slides of family[1 of 2] (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - 330 original and duplicate color slides of Mexico 1970 project (Huichol, Totonaca, Lacandon Maya, Tzotzil) and other slides of family[2 of 2] (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - 4 mounted b/w & colorized prints. Totonaca Indians. Tuxpam, Veracruz, Mex. Ceremoma del Palo Volador. 1970. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - 9 large b/ w lix 14" prints. San Cristobal de las Casas, Chiapas, Mex. Also, Joigelito & Zinacantan municipios. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - 13 Huichol Indian prints. El Colorin village, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mexico. 1970. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - 1 b/ w print of Jorge Paniagua's daughter. Lacanja Chan Sayab, Selva Lacandona, Chiapas, Mexico. 1970. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - 1 print of Mexican man in Mexico City, DF. by Tomas Mendoza Harrell. 1970. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - 3 mounted prints of Lacanja Chan Sayab, selva Lacandona. Chiapas, Mex. 1970. (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Series 7: Audio-Visual Materials
  - Subseries 1: Audio Tapes
    - Subsubseries 1: Performances and Interviews with Poets and Writers
      - Alurista "Cantos y Flores" 1974 (damaged tape), Circa 1973-4 / Songwriting texts. (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Evengelina Fernandez, actor, member of Teatro de la Esperanza, Interview. And Anita? At Point Bonita, Sausalito area, during the 11th TENAZ Teatro Chicano Festival held at the Mission Cultural Center in the Mission District, SF. 9/ 17/81 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Yo Puedo Migrant Education Student Summer Program. Univ. Calif. Santa Cruz. Creative Writing class taught by Juan Felipe Herrera. 7/24/84. (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Gato [Alejandro Murgufa]: On the Pocho-Che Collective, 60's-70's Chicano and Latino political writing collective in San francisco: 12/7/84 [1 of 2] (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Gato [Alejandro Murgufa]: On the Pocho-Che Collective, 60's-70's Chicano and Latino political writing collective in San Francisco: 1/3/85 [2 of 2] (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Interview of Juan Felipe Herrera by Margarita Luna Robles (San Francisco, CA. Mission District) After National Endowment for the Arts Award (1/85) for El Observador Spanish language periodical in San Jose, Ca. 1/14/85 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera. Poetry Reading. 4/27/85. (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera and John Ashbury, poetry reading at the Bisbee Poetry Festival. Bisbee, Arizona. 8/1985 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Casa Macondo Café poetry reading. Mission District, SF. John Martinez, Victor Martinez & John Nwoko (Nigerian poet). Informal taping by J F Herrera. 5/6/86. (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Martin Espada 6/26/1986 at Small Press Traffic, Mission District, SF. / Reading. (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - "At the Annex" Poetry & Jazz readings in San Jose, California. San Pedro Square. Organized by Margarita Luna Robles and Juan Felipe. 11/20/87[sides 1 and 2] (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - At the Annex/ Poetry Reading. 11/20/87. Juan Felipe Herrera, Margarita Luna Robles, with musicians from the First Street Project Jazz Band. San Jose, Ca. Genny Lim, devorah major, Francis Wong. [side 3] (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Flor y Canto Poetry Festival at Casa Zapata, Stanford 1987. [1 of 4] (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Flor y Canto Poetry Festival at Casa Zapata, Stanford 1987. [2 of 4] (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Flor y Canto Poetry Festival at Casa Zapata, Stanford 1987. [3 of 4] (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Flor y Canto Poetry Festival at Casa Zapata, Stanford 1987. [4 of 4] (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Jorge Lujan. Mexican Poet, singer, composer. Co-founder of Grupo Baul de Luna. Mexico City. Early 80's. These are musical arrangements of three of J F Herrera's poems set to music by Lujan. (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Encuentro Popular Festival. SF. Mission District. Mid 80's. (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Jose Antonio Burciaga. Stanford. late 80's. (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - Joaquin Ramon Ryan. (Son). Tapes of his writings, music, songs, verbal art, performance, 1987-1997. Pink Floyd [1 of 5] (Box 66, Folder 20)
      - Joaquin Ramon Ryan. (Son). Tapes of his writings, music, songs, verbal art, performance, 1987-1997. Nervosa [2 of 5] (Box 66, Folder 21)
      - Joaquin Ramon Ryan. (Son). Tapes of his writings, music, songs, verbal art, performance, 1987-1997. In My Life [3 of 5] (Box 66, Folder 22)
      - Joaquin Ramon Ryan. (Son). Tapes of his writings, music, songs, verbal art, performance, 1987-1997. Boxtops [4 of 5] (Box 66, Folder 23)
      - Joaquin Ramon Ryan. (Son). Tapes of his writings, music, songs, verbal art, performance, 1987-1997.Terrible Heart [5 of 5] (Box 66, Folder 24)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera. "Dreamboxer" One Man Show at Citylights Theatre. Rehearsal Tape. 1988. (Box 66, Folder 25)
      - Jorge Calderon, Jorge Herrera, Juan Felipe Herrera. 7/22/89. Radio Program with interviews and poetry. KPFA, Berkeley [side 1]. KPOO Poesia/ Juan F. Herrera 8/3/89, 6-7 pm: La Migra y Musica Michoacana [side 2] (Box 66, Folder 26)
      - "Native Tongue" final edits for Cassette production project (with Alejandro Murguia, devorah major, QR Hand and other Mission District poets with music) 11/ 17/89 [1 of 2] (Box 66, Folder 27)
      - "Native Tongue" final edits for Cassette production project (with Alejandro Murguia, devorah major, QR Hand and other Mission District poets with music) 11/ 17/89. [2 of 2][the tape box insert states Side A is "final edit," but Side A label on tape states "When Miles Apart by Amiri Baraka] (Box 66, Folder 28)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera. Sound poems: Arrivals - Fragments [1989?] [1 of 4] (Box 66, Folder 29)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera. Sound poems: Lakandon Avion [original sound track mix from 1970 journey to Chiapas][2 of 4] (Box 66, Folder 30)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera. Sound poems: Free The Living, Find the Dead, sound design for a play. Univ. of Iowa. 1989 [3 of 4] (Box 66, Folder 31)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera. Sound poems: Free The Living, Find the Dead, sound design for a play. Univ. of Iowa. 1989 [4 of 4]. (Box 66, Folder 32)
      - Gerald Stern. Poet. Interview. Iowa City, IA. At Gerry's porch. 1990, Spring. [1 of 2] (Box 66, Folder 33)
      - Gerald Stern. Poet. Interview. Iowa City, IA. At Gerry's porch. 1990, Spring. [2 of 2] (Box 66, Folder 34)
      - "New Letters on the Air" radio program for National Public radio, taped by Rebeka Presson. Poems. 1990 [1 of 2]. (Box 66, Folder 35)
      - "New Letters on the Air" radio program for National Public radio, taped by Rebeka Presson. Poems. 1990 [2 of 2]. (Box 66, Folder 36)
      - Samel Ruiz Garcia (Bishop of San Cristobal de Las Casas, Chiapas, Mex. Interview by Jorge Herrera. 4/24/92 [1 of 2]. (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Samel Ruiz Garcia (Bishop of San Cristobal de Las Casas, Chiapas, Mex. Interview by Jorge Herrera. 4/24/92 [2 of 2]. (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - John Irving. Novelist. Lecture. Breadloaf Writer's Conference. Middlebury, Vermont. 8/90. Taped by JFH [1 of 2] (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - John Irving. Novelist. Lecture. Breadloaf Writer's Conference. Middlebury, Vermont. 8/90. Taped by JFH [2 of 2] (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Poets Around the River. San Antonio Poets.[1990-1991] (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera and Marc Daterman (guitar), poems recorded in studio at Portland, Oregon while on tour for the Mt. Hood Writers Series. 1/24/92. (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera. Millwauki. 5/15/92. (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - George Barlow, poet 7/7/92 Interview African-American Poet discusses 60's and 70's Bay Area Scene (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Victor Martinez. Poet, novelist. 7/8/92. Interviews in SF. [1 of 2] (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Victor Martinez. Poet, novelist. 7/8/92. Interviews in SF. [2 of 2] (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Alfonso Macial, Interview 7/8/92. Former Pocho-Che poetry collective associate, Bay Area and also director of the Mission Cultural Center in the Mission District, SF. [1 of 2] (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Alfonso Macial, Interview 7/21/92. Former Pocho-Che poetry collective associate, Bay Area and also director of the Mission Cultural Center in the Mission District, SF. (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Jorge Herrera. 7/9/92. Chicano poet. SF. Founder of Pajaro Latinoamericano Radio program (KPOO) [1 of 2]. (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Jorge Herrera. 7/9/92. Chicano poet. SF. Founder of Pajaro Latinoamericano Radio program (KPOO) [2 of 2]. (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Tede Matthews, poet 7/21/92 (deceased) Interview discusses Gay poetry scene - "The Hula Palace" in the Castro, the Latino connection, Modern Times Bookstore poetry reading series history, the Mission District Lit scene. (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Jose Antonio Burciaga, poet 7/22/92 [2 tapes interview], at his house in Stanford University, Casa Zapata. Deceased. [1 of 2] (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Jose Antonio Burciaga, poet 7/22/92 [2 tapes interview], at his house in Stanford University, Casa Zapata. Deceased. [2 of 2] (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Larry Brown. Novelist. 12/1/92. Talk for J F Herrera's Creative Writing Class. Southern Illinois University - Carbondale. (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Juan Felipe Herrera poetry reading at Loyola Marymount University Reading organized by poet, critic and friend, Aldon Nielson 2/5/98 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - "The House That Couldn't Find the Street." Juan Felipe Herrera's Chicano Literature class (CSU-Fresno) reciting short stories on their childhood. 3/98. Fresno. (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Poetry Reading at Casa Zapata,, Stanford. Janice Mirikitani, David Piper, Jose Antonio Burciaga. [n.d] (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - Bay Area: El Tecolote Latino Newspaper Benefit. Mission District, San Francisco, Ca. Bookworks bookstore. 9/17/83. Writers: JFH, Domitila Canek, Merle Woo, Wilfredo Castano. (recorded by Bobby Paramo), 1/4"xl800ft. [1 of 5] (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Bay Area: El Tecolote Latino Newspaper Benefit. Mission District, San Francisco, Ca. Bookworks bookstore. 9/17/83. Writers: Jose Antonio Burciaga, Tede Matthews, Steppen Kessler, Clyde Salazar, Steve Abbott, Nellie Wong(recorded by Bobby Paramo), 1/4"xl800ft. [2 of 5] (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Bay Area: El Tecolote Latino Newspaper Benefit. Mission District, San Francisco, Ca. Bookworks bookstore. 9/17/83. Writers: Bernice Zantora, Victor Martinez, Margarita Luna Robles, Grupo Pedrada, Alejandro Murguia (recorded by Bobby Paramo), 1/4"xl800ft. [1 of 5] (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Bay Area: El Tecolote Latino Newspaper Benefit. Mission District, San Francisco, Ca. Bookworks bookstore. 9/17/83. Writers:. Jorge Herrera, Lucha Corpi, Jose Montoya, David Volpendesta & Barbara Paschke, John Martinez, Roberto Bedoya (recorded by Bobby Paramo), 1/4"xl800ft. [4 of 5] (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Bay Area: El Tecolote Latino Newspaper Benefit. Mission District, San Francisco, Ca. Bookworks bookstore. 9/17/83. Writers: Max Schwartz, Steve Heilman, JFH (recorded by Bobby Paramo), 1/4"xl800ft. [5 of 5] (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Stanford Reading: 1980's (recorded by Marylin Mulford) (Casa Zapata): Margarita Luna Robles, Linda?, Ruben Martinez, Margarita Luna Robles, Jorge Herrera (#2 is missing) (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Stanford Reading: 1980's (recorded by Marylin Mulford) (Casa Zapata): JFH, Sesshu Foster & JFH, Laura del Fuego, Gloria Trevino (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Stanford Reading: 1980's (recorded by Marylin Mulford) (Casa Zapata): Gloria Trevino, Javier Pacheco, Jorge Gonzalez (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Stanford Reading: 1980's (recorded by Marylin Mulford) (Casa Zapata): Jorge Gonzalez, Naomi Quinoes (Clark?), Gloria Alvarez ? (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Stanford Reading: 1980's (recorded by Marylin Mulford) (Casa Zapata): Gloria Alvarez, Margarita Luna Robles, Sesshu Foster, East LA Poet; Margarita Luna Robles (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Subsubseries 2: Indian Mexico
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [1 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [2 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [3 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [4 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [5 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [6 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [7 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [8 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Zinacantan, Chiapas: Interviews, music, live sound in households. 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [9 of 9] (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Tuxpam. Veracruz. Totonaca Indians: Ceremoma del Palo Volador. Sever San Martin, elder Totonaca (from Poza Rica). 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [1 of 4] (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Tuxpam. Veracruz. Totonaca Indians: Ceremoma del Palo Volador. Sever San Martin, elder Totonaca (from Poza Rica). 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [2 of 4] (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Tuxpam. Veracruz. Totonaca Indians: Ceremoma del Palo Volador. Sever San Martin, elder Totonaca (from Poza Rica). 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [3 of 4] (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Tuxpam. Veracruz. Totonaca Indians: Ceremoma del Palo Volador. Sever San Martin, elder Totonaca (from Poza Rica). 9/1970 1/4/x600ft [4 of 4] (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Joigelito, Chiapas: Drums, flute and song in the village. Sunday ceremonies. 9/70. 1/4/x600ft [1 of 2] (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Joigelito, Chiapas: Drums, flute and song in the village. Sunday ceremonies. 9/70. 1/4/x600ft [2 of 2] (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - El Colorin, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mexico (& Tepic, Nayarit [ Huichol Canciones]): Huichol Indians: Ramon Medina Silva, Huichol Maraakame (Shaman) explains history, music and culture of the Huichol and plays music. 1/4/x600ft [1 of 7] (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - El Colorin, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mexico (& Tepic, Nayarit [ Huichol Canciones]): Huichol Indians: Ramon Medina Silva, Huichol Maraakame (Shaman) explains history, music and culture of the Huichol and plays music. 1/4/x600ft [2 of 7] (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - El Colorin, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mexico (& Tepic, Nayarit [ Huichol Canciones]): Huichol Indians: Ramon Medina Silva, Huichol Maraakame (Shaman) explains history, music and culture of the Huichol and plays music. 1/4/x600ft [3 of 7] (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - El Colorin, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mexico (& Tepic, Nayarit [ Huichol Canciones]): Huichol Indians: Ramon Medina Silva, Huichol Maraakame (Shaman) explains history, music and culture of the Huichol and plays music. 1/4/x600ft [4 of 7] (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - El Colorin, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mexico (& Tepic, Nayarit [ Huichol Canciones]): Huichol Indians: Ramon Medina Silva, Huichol Maraakame (Shaman) explains history, music and culture of the Huichol and plays music. 1/4/x600ft [5 of 7] (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - El Colorin, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mexico (& Tepic, Nayarit [ Huichol Canciones]): Huichol Indians: Ramon Medina Silva, Huichol Maraakame (Shaman) explains history, music and culture of the Huichol and plays music. 1/4/x600ft [6 of 7] (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - El Colorin, Nayar Mountains, Nayarit, Mexico (& Tepic, Nayarit [ Huichol Canciones]): Huichol Indians: Ramon Medina Silva, Huichol Maraakame (Shaman) explains history, music and culture of the Huichol and plays music. 1/4/x600ft [7 of 7] (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Naja Air Arrival. Naha, one of two remaining Lacandon Maya villages in the rain forest of Chiapas, Mexico. (1) tape. 1/4/x600ft (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified audiotape. 1/4," 7" reel (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 2: Video Tape and Film
    - Mayan, Totonaca 16mm b/ w rush print footage. Journey to Mexico, 1970. Filmed by Tomas Mendoza Harrell, JFH. Edited by Mendoza Harrell. (Copied to video: 3/4" U-Matic). 44 min. [3/14/90] (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - JFH giving poetry workshop to Florisong poetry collective in San Jose, Ca. Content, Rhythm, Pattern, Sound. (8/21/82). Filmed by Margarita Luna Robles. (3/4" U-Matic) (Box 71, Folder 2)